export const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "What was the name of the pre-Saved by the Bell series that featured Zack, Screech, and Lisa?",
    options: [
      `Mr. Belding's World`,
      `Life From Bayside High`,
      `Good Morning, Miss Bliss`,
      `High School Never Ends`
    ],
    correct: `Good Morning, Miss Bliss`
  },
  {
    question: "What did A.C. stand for?",
    options: [
      `Albert Clifford Slater`,
      `Alexander Carl Slater`,
      `Absolutely Charming Slater`,
      `Andres Caleb Slater`
    ],
    correct: `Albert Clifford Slater`
  },
  {
    question: "Who did Kelly break up with Zack for in season two?",
    options: [`A.C. Slater`, `Johnny Dakota`, `Screech`, `Jeffrey Hunter`],
    correct: `Jeffrey Hunter`
  },
  {
    question:
      "What did Zack always say before the show froze and he analyzed the situation around him?",
    options: [`Freeze!`, `Time out!`, `Hold up!`, `Pause!`],
    correct: `Time out!`
  },
  {
    question: `An argument over which two opoosing interests leads Jessie and Slater to break up?`,
    options: [
      `Ballet versus football`,
      `Tofu versus steak`,
      `Vests versus Zubaz`,
      `Sitting in chairs properly versus sitting in chairs backwards`
    ],
    correct: "Ballet versus football"
  },
  {
    question: `What's the name of the beach club where Zack falls in love with Stacey Carosi during season three`,
    options: [
      `North Beach Club`,
      `Beverly Hills Atlantic Beach Club`,
      `Bayside Beach Club`,
      `Malibu Sands Beach Club`
    ],
    correct: "Malibu Sands Beach Club"
  },
  {
    question: `What kind of car was Zack trying to buy from Mr. Carosi?`,
    options: [
      `1963 Corvette Stingray`,
      `1966 Shelby Cobra`,
      `1966 Mustang`,
      `1969 Dodge Charger`
    ],
    correct: "1966 Mustang"
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of Valley High's mascot?`,
    options: ["Bulldogs", "Tigers", "Lions", "Panthers"],
    correct: "Bulldogs"
  },
  {
    question: `What do Lisa's parents do for a living?`,
    options: [
      `They're both doctors`,
      `Mom's doctor, dad's a lawyer`,
      `Mom's a lawyer, dad's a doctor`,
      `They're both lawyers`
    ],
    correct: `They're both doctors`
  },
  {
    question:
      "At the end of season three, a few of the kids work at the mall to make some money before the holidays. They all have various jobs, but where does Slater work?",
    options: [
      "Dressed as Santa Claus",
      "The gift-wrapping stand",
      "The food court",
      `Moody's Store For Men`
    ],
    correct: "The gift-wrapping stand"
  },
  {
    question: `What did Slater crash into while driving the driver's ed car, injuring Kelly's head in the process?`,
    options: ["Lockers", "Nerds", "A chalkboard", "A vending machine"],
    correct: "Lockers"
  },
  {
    question: `Why does Mr. Belding's cool brother Rod ditch a planned field trip with the kids?`,
    options: [
      `He's got a job interview`,
      `He's got a date with a stewardess`,
      `He's got to score some speed`,
      `He's going to see Motley Crue`
    ],
    correct: `He's got a date with a stewardess`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the girl Slater fell in love with while the group was in Palm Springs for Jessie's dad's wedding?`,
    options: ["Kimberly", "Samantha", "Christina", "Leslie"],
    correct: "Christina"
  },
  {
    question: "Where did Zack, Kelly, Slater, and Screech attend college?",
    options: ["Stanford", "UCLA", "USC", "Cal U"],
    correct: "Cal U"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which one of these titles was NOT the name of a Saved by the Bell spinoff show or movie?",
    options: [
      "Saved by the Bell: Hawaiian Style",
      "Saved by the Bell: The Glory Days",
      "Saved by the Bell: Wedding in Las Vegas",
      "Saved by the Bell: The College Years"
    ],
    correct: "Saved by the Bell: The Glory Days"
  }
];
